Hey, it's me again, your Sebastian,
こんにちは また会いましたね セバスチャンです
and we are now ready for the highlight of the entire nanodegree program,
Capstone プロジェクトである Nanodegree プログラム全体の
which is your Capstone Project.
ハイライトが用意できました
This is a project in which you build the software for the entire self-driving car
これは皆さんが自動運転車全体のソフトウェアを end-to-end でビルドするプロジェクトです
end-to-end either in simulation or actually on a physical caveat here in Mountain View.
シミュレーション または ここ Mountain View で実物の車を使って行います
My recommendation is you obviously can do it on your
私のお勧めはこれを明らかに自分でシミュレーションでき
own on simulation and pass this Capstone Project.
この Capstone プロジェクトに合格することです
But there's an option to do as a team and I would
ただし チームとして行う選択肢もあり
really highly recommend to do as a team for many reasons.
多くの理由からチームとして行うことを強くお勧めします
First reason, in any self-driving car company,
まず 自動運転車を扱う会社では
you have to work in teams.
チームで働く必要があるからです
You might as well learn how to work in teams. Second, it's fun.
ですからチームの中で働く方法も学習できるでしょう2 つ目の理由は楽しいからです
You get to meet lot of people.
たくさんの人と出会えます
You get to learn from them and we can teach them something new.
その人たちから学んだり その人たちに何か新しいことを教えたりできます
Finally, for those who finish the Capstone Project in teams,
最後に Capstone プロジェクトをチームで終えた人には
we have this extra benefit,
特別な特典があります
that we will run your software on a physical, wheel,
皆さんのソフトウェアを物理的なタイヤの付いた車で
car here in Mountain View,
この Mountain View を走らせることになります
so you can go to any future friend and employer and brag about
ですから将来友人や従業員に 皆さんのソフトウェアが実際の
that your software has an actual physical self-driving car.
物理的な自動運転車についたことを自慢できます
How cool is that?
すごくないですか?